openxcell.com 2011-12-17

# Privacy Policy

_openxcell.com_

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Your privacy is important to OpenXcell Technolabs. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that OpenXcell Technolabs collects, and the ways in which OpenXcell Technolabs Pvt. Ltd. uses that personal information.

## Using personal information

OpenXcell Technolabs Pvt. Ltd. may use your personal information to:

  * send you marketing communications.
  * send you statements and invoices, and
  * supply to you services that you purchase. 

Where OpenXcell Technolabs Pvt. Ltd. discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, OpenXcell Technolabs Pvt. Ltd. may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

## Securing your data

OpenXcell Technolabs Pvt. Ltd. will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

OpenXcell Technolabs Pvt. Ltd. will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

[Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.]

## Cross-border data transfers

Information that OpenXcell Technolabs Pvt. Ltd. collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which OpenXcell Technolabs Pvt. Ltd. operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

## Updating this statement

OpenXcell Technolabs Pvt. Ltd. may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

## Other websites

This website contains links to other websites.

OpenXcell Technolabs Pvt. Ltd. is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

## Contact OpenXcell Technolabs Pvt. Ltd.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or OpenXcell Technolab’s treatment of your personal information, please write to:

  * by email to admin@openxcell.com or
  * by post to 87, Suryodaya Bunglows, Opp Gulab Tower, Thaltej, Ahmadabad – 61, Gujarat, India.
